A makeover project
for your most unhinged leftovers.
The best chefs in Korea will
turn your fridge inside out.
The classy cooking show has returned.
-Chef & My Fridge!
-My Fridge!
-Welcome.
-Welcome. It's great to see you all.
I see a few unfamiliar faces.
The studio is crowded today.
It's too crowded.
We actually prepared
a very special team round today.
CURIOUS
Instead of teaming up
two existing cast members,
we've invited
two chefs' actual team members.
The actual employees at their restaurants?
We invited their right-hand men
and put together a new kind of team round.
-Sounds fun.
-We made it happen.
It didn't happen suddenly, though.
-So we planned it since last summer?
-Yes, you're right.
Hyun-suk and I had a chance
to cook together,
and during that event,
we thought it'd be fun
to compete in these teams on the show.
And it happened.
THE TEAM ROUND IS FINALLY HAPPENING
Hyun-suk's right-hand man,
can you tell us about yourself?
Before he does that,
let me blot out his nose first.
-Look how nice he is.
-How sweet.
-He has to look good on the screen.
-Did he just flinch?
-A little.
-I think he flinched a bit.
He must've thought he was getting punched.
Please say hello.
Hello, I am head chef Kim Seon-yeop,
who's been working
with Chef Hyun-suk for 14 years.
THE HEAD CHEF OF CHOI DOT
How does it feel to be here?
I can't believe I'm here,
the destination all chefs dream of.
-"The destination."
-This is the destination?
Many young chefs dream
of being on Chef & My Fridge.
So many.
It was the destination for chefs?
DREAMS COME TRUE
I first met him as a student back in 2012.
How many years is that?
And now, he feels like my other self,
someone I can't work without.
That's Chef Kim Seon-yeop.
If he's worked with you for 14 years,
it already proves his character.
-That's true.
-You must be one patient man.
Such long years.
-How did he hold out?
-You're something.
Once I retire, I wouldn't even mind
passing my position to him.
Really?
-Step down!
-Step down, Hyun-suk!
Can you punch him once?
NEEDS HIS RIGHT-HAND MAN'S HELP
Why don't we meet
Chef Jong-won's right-hand man too?
-He's also good-looking.
-Isn't he?
Doesn't he remind you
of Jung Hyuk, the model?
THE RESEMBLANCE IS THERE
Why don't you say hello too?
Hello.
I am Woo Do-hee,
and I work at L'Amant Secret.
I've always enjoyed this show
since my days as a military cook.
-You were a mess cook?
-Yes, I was.
He was a mess cook too.
Great to meet you.
A BIG SMILE TO SHOW HIS GLADNESS
-I don't know why, but I like him.
-A military cook.
Tell us about him, Jong-won.
He's been working with me
for three years now.
He's someone who makes up
for the things I lack.
-I always know that he has my back.
-So you can trust him.
Jong-won, do you only hire
those who have a similar hairstyle?
-I don't care about looks, but hair, yes.
-The hair.
ONE CONDITION: GOOD HAIR VIBES
Chef Do-hee is nicknamed
Dupe Jong-won.
-Dupe Jong-won?
-What's this about?
Well, the lighting is rather low
at our restaurant,
and our silhouettes are similar,
so some guests take me for him.
They have similar builds.
So are their silhouettes.
-People must go, "Jong-won is here."
-"He's here."
At first, they whisper,
then they look disappointed
when I approach.
SORRY TO DISAPPOINT
So people at L'Amant Secret
call him Chef de Disappointment.
-It's supposed to be "cuisine."
-Not chef de cuisine.
He has a great physique, doesn't he?
So some call him Wide-Shouldered, WS.
You're right. Look at his biceps.
When it comes to shoulders,
-this guy's even bigger than Ma Dong-seok.
-Right.
-He has
-Ma Dong-seok of the culinary world.
-the craziest back.
-Yes, you're right.
-He's no joke, right? Hey, Poong.
-Really.
You'll end up in diapers
once he punches you with these.
-I get it.
-Don't get smart with me.
FEELING CONFIDENT WITH A SIDEKICK
Actually, I was a bit worried.
After all, Chef & My Fridge
is a show that is meant to entertain,
but this guy has too much respect for me.
He jokes around a lot
and is funny when he's alone,
but with me,
he only shows respect, respect, respect.
So I told our scriptwriter
we'd give up on entertaining
and only focus on cooking this time
-because he's with me.
-He won't let him talk.
Can you step outside for a moment then?
We want to have
a fun chat with Chef Seon-yeop.
We get that you respect him,
but what if you had to single out
one weakness that he has?
HESITANT
He tends to…
SEON-YEOP!
He tends to fish for praise.
Whoa. He fishes for compliments.
-He tends to do that.
-He talks perfectly well.
-What do you mean, only respect?
-He's good.
UNCOVERING THE TRUTH WITH A KIND SMILE
What specific thing did I do
to fish for praise?
THE WORST QUESTION
He doesn't know what he did.
Thanks to me,
he got to travel around the world.
He must've dreaded it so much.
CATHARTIC
He absolutely does fish for it.
PRAISE FISHER CHOI
I've watched them
in the kitchen as a third party,
and Chef Seon-yeop
once let out the biggest sigh
from the bottom of his heart and said,
"I should do it."
He said it with such a deep sigh.
-"I should do it."
-I've seen him let out that deep sigh.
-He has a lot to tell.
When our production crew
called him for a pre-interview,
he would not hang up.
Gosh, it usually isn't that long.
He had things he wanted to share.
-We have the transcript of the call.
-We do?
Chef Seon-yeop said,
"I'll probably end up
only cleaning up his mess."
That means that's what he always does!
How should we perceive this?
When he cooks,
he tends to make a mess.
AN EXPERT AT MAKING A MESS
-Unlike Chef Jong-won, who always wipes.
-He does.
SUDDENLY STOPS TALKING…
Fifteen minutes are already fairly short,
so I thought I'd end up
only cleaning up after him.
Things weren't too different on this side.
-What?
-He also spent
-all night on the phone with our crew.
-Are you serious?
What did he have to say?
He's scary.
He said, "I'm often surprised
while watching Chef & My Fridge."
"He often flies off the handle
when he's with us,
so it's really strange
to see him seem so shy on the show."
He must feel like a stranger!
How should we take this?
How is he different?
-Is he mad?
-I think
-he's a tough guy in the kitchen.
-A tough guy.
It's a rare sight
to see him seem shy at work,
-so it's strange.
-So he's not like that at all?
Last time, he did the strikeout thing.
Did you watch that episode?
-Yes, the strikeout pose.
-I did.
I got
-secondhand embarrassment watching him.
-Yes, I'm sure.
CRINGED HARD
WHILE WATCHING HIS BOSS AT WORK
-Jong-won looks flushed.
-He doesn't know what to do.
It's an emergency.
I think it's my job
to entertain people
when I'm shooting the show.
-I've been doing my best.
-Yes, you're trying.
Chef Do-hee feels
secondhand embarrassment, right?
This guy says
he always feels secondhand pride
-through me.
-Secondhand pride.
Why do you
keep saying these things yourself?
Stop it!
-He just sighed.
-See? I told you so.
-That was such a loud sigh.
-You tell them. You can relax and talk.
He can't seem to relax,
so how is he supposed to do that?
Will you just let him talk?
HAS LOTS TO SAY BUT WON'T
I'm looking forward to today.
-We don't know what the order is.
-But they will compete.
Yes, that's decided.
-Let's invite today's guests now.
-The guests.
They're people that we all hoped
would come and dine with us,
and they found time to join us today
despite their busy schedule.
Please welcome today's fridge owners!
Come on out!
Today's fridge owners.
Welcome!
-KARINA and WINTER of aespa!
-It's great to see you!
STANDING OVATION
-I'm blushing.
-Please welcome
KARINA and WINTER of aespa!
Welcome to the show!
WELCOME
WELCOMING PASSIONATELY
Oh, man.
I can't believe
I'm meeting you two in person.
Let us greet you. Two, three.
-Hello, we're aespa.
Oh, man.
Will you stop saying that?
How many times do you have to say that?
Oh, man. Seriously.
I have K-pop idol experts at home,
so I was already educated.
Why don't you meet the new chefs
and say hello to them too?
-Right.
-Hello.
SAYING HI TO THE OTHER SIDE
Their faces lit up instantly.
HAPPY
SLAPPING THE RIGHT-HAND MAN
Seon-yeop!
I should prick your ears
to make them less red.
-He's so red.
-He's blushing more and more.
I got to check how many teeth you have.
You have great teeth.
I heard that you two
really love Chef & My Fridge.
-We're huge fans.
-You are?
And now that I'm actually here,
it feels so cool.
GIGGLE
And the same for us.
We find it so cool too.
WINTER, you've watched us
-since your early teens?
-You did?
Yes, it must've been 2014.
-I was in middle school.
-We started back then.
I'd watch it over a meal with my mom.
I remember us both getting mesmerized
at how the chefs cooked.
-And that teen grew up to be here.
-Right?
NOW SHE'S ON THE SHOW
-That's true.
-Anyway, KARINA.
-I heard you came very determined.
-Is that so?
Yes, I plan
to go very far today.
-You plan to go very far?
-Why would a guest do that?
I really enjoyed Ye-eun's episode
as well as Yu-jin's episode.
I hope our episodes are the funniest.
THAT'S AESPA'S SPIRIT
I knew it.
-We're here to be funny for you!
-Yes.
We can make it funny. We'll do it.
WOW…
What if I asked you to come with me
for the five-minute check?
If you'd like, of course.
-I'm ready for it.
-Are you?
-You're in?
-Yes.
-And WINTER? Great.
-I'm ready too.
I heard KARINA prepared
a party trick for us.
You prepared a party trick?
-She's prepared.
-It's not that.
-This is big.
-Really?
Can we see it?
I'm sure you had been busy
promoting your new album.
-So?
-Well, it's…
We often say
people clap like fur seals, right?
So I came up with the seal clap.
-The seal clap?
CHUCKLE…
Is it already funny?
SO MUCH PRESSURE
-I think it'll be really funny.
-Don't expect too much.
But please laugh out loud for me.
-Yes, of course.
-No worries!
EVERYONE BEGINS TO LAUGH
I'm ready to die from laughing.
MOVED
Okay. I'll do it.
CHUCKLE
LAUNCH THE SEAL CLAP
LAUNCH THE REACTION
I'M SO GRATEFUL FOR HIM…
GOOD ONE
That was funny.
THE ADDICTIVE SEAL CLAP
-I'm feeling hot now.
-Thanks for that.
Actually, there's an actual seal
on our show.
Is there a seal among us?
Ho-young's pretty much an actual seal.
Can you do this for us?
JUST LIKE A SEAL
He can do it right away.
You can't steal it from me.
Do you have anything, WINTER?
WONDERING…
Yes! I can…
I just thought of something.
I can rotate my hand 360 degrees.
360 DEGREES?
-Your hand?
-Hand?
-Her hand?
-Let me show you.
Rotate it all the way?
-Most people can do this, right?
-Yes.
I can flip it again.
I CAN EVEN ROTATE IT TOO
-What?
-What was that?
Wait a minute. How flexible are you?
-How did she do that?
-I just can.
HOW DID SHE DO THAT?
LIKE THIS?
How does she flip it this way?
OUCH…
-You have to cook later.
-Please be careful.
That's why she could
do this dance so naturally.
That could be a surprising party trick.
-Good start.
-Off to a great start.
WE GOT THIS
Also, I hear WINTER
has a teacher among the chefs.
-Hey.
-Really?
-Did I?
-"Did I?"
It might be true or not. So who is it?
-Chef Sung-jun is my teacher, actually.
-What?
-He is? Sung-jun?
-Yes.
Don't open your eyes like that. Please.
What did you possibly learn from him?
A while back, Sung-jun said
he'd send me pistachio cream.
He said he'd send it to me.
-But he never did.
-Come on.
-He didn't?
-Why didn't you?
Boo.
But I didn't have your address.
-You could've sent it to her agency.
-Her agency.
-To her agency?
-Yes.
Right-o.
SUNG-JUN DE DISAPPOINTMENT…
On top of that, I wasn't his best student.
-He has someone else?
-Yes.
He outright told me I was second place.
-She'd mostly be everyone's first.
-Right?
Did you have to say that?
-That's the worst.
-Actually,
I do have one student I cherish,
someone who is very good at cooking.
I also wish we could have him here,
someone named Faker.
-Just be second place.
-Yes, the professional gamer.
-Quiet.
-He's an excellent cook.
Is he really?
So I'm here to look for a new teacher.
GREAT NEWS
-A new chef?
-Do that.
Just find someone new.
Sung-jun isn't the only chef
you can learn from.
-Right, everyone here can be a teacher.
-Emergency.
Her teacher is always
looking for a new teacher too.
-You're right.
-Yes.
-Like teacher, like student.
-Emergency.
-I'll find a new teacher today.
-See if you want anyone else.
Is there anyone you're considering?
I considered
Chef Hyun-suk or…
He's on her radar.
-Right hand down, please.
-Yes, please.
HEHE
-Or Chef Sam.
-Sam.
-Why did you skip me just like that?
-No!
Poong was right in the middle.
-He's right there, but she skipped him.
-I was even looking at her.
You just aren't it.
-I'm sure WINTER will find…
-Of course.
…her new teacher after today's cook-offs.
aespa is from the famous agency,
SM Entertainment,
-and they are their flagship group.
-Yes.
WE'RE THE FLAGSHIP GROUP?
And these two are known to have
the textbook SM Entertainment look.
-They do.
-I think WINTER
was definitely born to be in SM.
-WINTER more than you?
-Yes.
She reminds me
of both Seo Hyun-jin and Taeyeon,
all very fair and…
They always include a member like that.
-I think it applies more to KARINA.
-Yes?
-Rather?
-It's like we're at a pageant.
-So KARINA has the textbook SM look?
-Yes, I think so.
I actually didn't make the cut
for the audition like three times.
I kept auditioning again and again
until I got in.
But in her case,
the agency contacted her first, via DM.
She was chosen by them,
whereas I chose the agency.
-So that's how people are cast now?
-They do that these days.
-Back in my day, it was on the streets.
-The streets.
People were cast on the streets.
-At Bupyeong Station or…
-Gangnam Station.
-Bupyeong Station?
-Bupyeong.
-Street dancers lurked there.
-You hung out at Bupyeong?
Lots of street dancers were there,
so they'd get picked up.
That's how people were picked up.
Wait a second.
I have a surprising transcript.
WINTER said one of the chefs
-had the typical SM Entertainment look.
-There is?
-One of you has that look.
-The SM Entertainment look?
Could it be Eun-yeong?
She looks quite hopeful.
GIGGLE
-Right. Cut it out.
-No way.
It's a great agency for idol stars.
-SM Entertainment sounds right.
So who has that look?
First, Chef Jong-won.
TYPICAL SM ENTERTAINMENT LOOK
-I can see it.
-Anyone else?
Chef Ho-young.
-Ho-young?
-What?
Ho-young?
-I can't agree.
-Are you saying this
-just to flatter him? Really?
-I'm serious.
There's always that one member
called the fan magnet.
-"Fan magnet"?
-Right.
-What's a fan magnet?
-That's a thing.
Is that a good thing?
-It is.
-It is?
-He has that look.
-There's that niche.
IF IT'S A GOOD THING, OKAY THEN
DEFINITELY THE FAN MAGNET
You two brought two separate fridges.
Do you live separately?
That's not the case.
We actually had two dorms
for two members each
but recently moved into one place.
We brought both fridges
from our previous places,
so we ended up with two.
They live in the same dorm,
but they use different fridges.
-Shall we?
-Let's go.
Let's go through WINTER's fridge.
I literally have nothing.
-You don't?
-All I kept in there were beverages
because I had no time to eat
back at the dorm.
But I recently started
to aim for a healthier lifestyle,
so I've been slowly filling it up.
I still might not have much.
We haven't even opened it.
-I feel so…
-Excuses.
-I feel anxious.
-Do you?
Wait, as you can see,
the shelf-stable ingredients
are all right in the middle.
Do you share these ingredients?
-Do you share these?
-We just
steal each other's food
whenever the other isn't looking.
AS STEALTHY AS THEIR CHOREOGRAPHY
-What's this?
-A ramyeon cooker.
-It's mine.
-KARINA's?
It's the famous
Hangang River ramyeon cooker.
My friend gave it to me
as a birthday present.
-Because you love ramyeon?
-Shows my power, doesn't it?
I love it so much.
So are these all yours?
Actually, among these
shelf-stable ingredients,
mine are just the cooker and alcohol.
Everything else is WINTER's.
-Everything else belongs to WINTER?
-That's right.
Do you see that scale?
-This one?
-That means someone in that house…
-You're right.
-…is an avid cook.
I'm sorry, but it's for body weight.
A JOKE JUST FOR GIRL GROUPS
-I guess they can do that.
-They're that light.
Right. For them?
-It's mine.
-Was she into baking?
I wanted to make Dubai chewy cookies
-and heard measuring is very important.
-You're right.
I'm always trying to cook.
Then for this episode and the next,
will WINTER only use her ingredients,
and KARINA only hers?
-We'll use them together.
-It sounds unfair, though.
AESPA IS ONE, WE CAN'T BE TWO
-Thank you!
-Right?
-It feels unfair.
-You can see truffle oil and stuff here.
-We present aespa WINTER's fridge!
-Fridge!
LUKEWARM RESPONSE
EMBARRASSED
PRESENTING WINTER'S FRIDGE
-There is some stuff.
-She has a few things.
I thought you'd only have beverages,
so this isn't too bad.
Yes, you have quite a lot.
She doesn't have too much,
but she put them on display nicely.
-She made it look fuller.
-She could've put it all on one shelf.
She spread it all out.
The second shelf has…
-Some side dishes.
-Korean banchan.
My mom made and sent them to me.
Delicious side dishes.
Where's your hometown?
-Yangsan.
-With Tongdosa Temple.
-Yes, Tongdosa Temple.
KNOWN FOR TONGDOSA TEMPLE
-The same word for sun umbrella.
-Right.
HA HA HA HA
ALSO GOING, HA HA HA
Was it that bad?
-He must be under so much pressure.
-That was so tacky.
-Makjang!
-Makjang?
-Is this your mom's writing?
-Yes, to prevent confusion.
-She labeled it.
-It's so good with chili pepper.
-Yes, or sundae, Korean sausage.
I ordered sundae in Seoul,
and it only came with salt.
WINTER IS MORE USED
TO EATING IT WITH MAKJANG
I need makjang with it.
Just as mandu, dumplings,
come with soy sauce,
sundae and makjang are always a given.
But all I got was salt in Seoul.
You must've been surprised
when you first got it.
I told them something was missing,
that the sauce wasn't here.
HOW CUTE
We don't serve it here.
I'm always like,
"How do you eat this? It's so bland."
WINTER'S DIALECT SLIPS OUT
-"How do you eat this…"
-We're hearing the dialect now.
"How do you eat this?"
It tasted so bland.
Do you get self-conscious
when you use your dialect?
-Just a little.
-A little bit? I see.
What are these? Pumpkin leaves.
-Pumpkin leaves?
-You have pumpkin leaves?
They're delicious when blanched,
when you use it as wrap for rice…
-Pumpkin leaves and rice?
-…and gang-doenjang, a doenjang dish.
People who are older than you
usually enjoy these veggie wraps.
I hear that I eat like a granny.
-You eat like a granny?
-A granny?
Not like a baby, but like a granny?
It's an emergency.
I like earthy, hearty dishes
like doenjang, cheonggukjang, biji-jjigae,
and even kong-guksu, cold soybean noodles.
-She eats like a granny.
-Like a granny.
Soybean leaves.
-Whoa.
-Soybean leaves.
-Really?
-I can easily finish a bowl of white rice
with those pickled leaves.
Perilla leaves.
She really loves things like these.
-You do eat like a granny.
-She does.
Tteok, rice cake. Do you enjoy these?
I often get my food delivered,
but I'm so impatient
and can't wait that long.
-I have to snack on something.
-I see.
-After ordering a meal?
-Yes.
I always need ice cream,
chips, or even tteok
to snack on while I wait.
But you wouldn't be able
to eat your meal after snacking.
-I still eat.
-Are you the type
who eats small portions often?
If we were runners,
I'd be considered a sprinter.
I like to scarf it all up
and then call it to an end.
But WINTER is a marathoner.
-Eating constantly?
-She keeps eating little by little.
She's Usain Bolt, and she's Lee Bong-ju.
DEFINITELY DIFFERENT EVENTS
When people like these eat together,
they can end up fighting.
YOU'RE RIGHT
-She'd have to wait for her.
-Yes.
When I feel full while eating my meal,
I take a break before I start over.
Because the food goes down a little
after some time.
By the time I go back,
-she'd be cleaning up.
-I'd clean up.
I often had to stop her like,
"I'm not done yet!"
What do you usually order?
-I've been hooked on mala xiang guo.
-Mala xiang guo.
-You even have this sauce.
-I do.
-Fen haozi noodles and all.
-She has it all.
When you order those noodles,
just two strands of those
would cost me 5,000 won.
-They're expensive.
-It's not cost-effective,
so I decided to buy it myself
and add it to the dish,
because I was going to order a lot anyway.
-You're frugal.
-She is.
Is aespa not doing well financially?
That's not the reason.
She's thrifty and knows how to save money.
It's great.
Actually, those noodles
are usually kept in the freezer.
But like I said, I'm impatient,
and they take too long to thaw.
I end up eating tteok and ice cream
while I wait for those to thaw.
-You are impatient.
-A bit.
Wait a second.
Are these all yours?
Because KARINA's are over there, right?
-There's… Makgeolli.
-Everything!
Beer, champagne, and wine.
-You have every kind.
-And soju.
-She failed to open this on the first try.
-This?
She failed and broke the cork,
so she cut it in half.
I can't take my alcohol too well,
but I still enjoy a bit of it.
-A drink with your meals?
-Like that.
-With your food?
-Yes, with my food.
-She likes a drink with her meals.
-But wait.
-She eats like a granny.
-A granny. That's why.
-You drink soju with your food?
-She drinks soju and makgeolli.
-Look. She's not done with it.
-She's not.
She puts the lid back on
after drinking some.
Wait, the writer clearly said
they'd replace them with new bottles.
EVERYTHING ON CHEF & MY FRIDGE IS CANDID
How long did it take to drink this much?
-I had that much in a day.
-In a day.
-Alone?
-A day.
-Alone.
-It happens.
Are you doing okay?
What's important here
is that you had a drink of soju
while eating your meal alone at home.
A COMFORT DRINK AFTER A TOUGH DAY
SO HOMEY
She had it alone.
Yes, sitting like a granny.
With rice wrapped in soybean leaves.
Like, "Why isn't KARINA home yet?"
-That's Yangsan style.
-Yangsan style.
It feels so approachable and nice.
Then do you two ever drink together?
There's a bench
in front of our dorm building,
-and we had beer there,
-A can of beer.
…with some gummy candy
we got at a convenience store and chatted.
Who can drink alcohol better?
Goodness.
-I wouldn't even dare.
-You wouldn't dare?
KARINA IS FAMOUS AS SOMEONE
WHO CAN HOLD HER LIQUOR
-You must like noodles too.
-I do.
What's your favorite noodle dish?
In the end, my favorite
noodle dish has to be pasta.
-I found some pasta sauce.
-Tomato sauce.
-You're right.
-Did you make some?
-No, not yet.
-She has it but doesn't exactly cook.
-She bought all these but never used them.
-She just felt motivated.
Our promotion just ended
after spending many busy days,
and we couldn't even return to the dorm,
so I forgot about the stuff
that I ordered.
-She had been busy.
-All she had was soju and…
JUST A GLASS OF SOJU?
Just soju, and nothing else?
That's kind of sexy.
Without any food?
-I do eat snacks.
-With your meal?
-You know, like kimchi.
-Kimchi?
-Soybean leaves?
You're that type?
Soju and kimchi are the real deal.
-I have a question.
-Soju and kimchi?
Do you pour your drink into a glass?
-Then would she drink out of the bottle?
-Out of the bottle.
TELL ME ABOUT IT
-Only she knows.
-But wait.
Do you all pour your drinks
even when you drink alone?
INTERPRETATION: OR IS IT JUST ME?
-I was just curious.
-You drink it out of the bottle?
She'd throw the bottle and go,
"Let me grab some kimchi."
WINTER AT HOME AFTER WORK
GRANNY, IT'S NICE TO DRINK ALONE,
BUT DO LOOK AFTER YOUR HEALTH
Do you enjoy meat?
Yes, I eat meat rather often.
From what I heard,
WINTER would do the grilling
when the members eat meat together.
-Yes.
-It's because
I'm that impatient.
As the most impatient one,
I grill it quickly so I can eat it.
I go, "Do you want this?
No? Then I'll eat it."
I personally don't like to grill meat,
so when she does it next to me, I go,
"This is so delicious. You're so good!"
And she gets very excited.
She goes, "Do you want more?"
"Am I good?"
You're trying to control her.
Not only are you impatient,
you've been praised into doing it.
-What could this be?
-It's frozen.
-Gejang, seasoned raw crab, in soy sauce?
-Gejang in soy sauce.
-My mom told me to keep it frozen.
-I wouldn't be able to hold myself back.
But I can't wait until it thaws,
so I haven't had it yet.
PLEASE GET BETTER
When you freeze it,
it's better to separate
the crabs from the sauce.
-Really?
-You can keep sauce in the kimchi fridge
and freeze the crabs separately.
That way, they'll thaw faster.
I see. That's a great life hack.
-So she's never had this.
-If you hate thawing that much,
just leave the freezer open
when you leave.
ANOTHER GREAT LIFE HACK?
It'll be thawed when you get home.
She can't do that.
She's way more impatient than I thought.
Especially when I'm hungry,
because I want
to eat something immediately.
I can't contain my hunger.
That must be why you like our show.
-Everything is so quick.
-In just 15 minutes.
-Right?
-Yes, so I love it.
We'll cook delicious meals for you
in just 15 minutes today.
That's all for WINTER's fridge!
-I didn't know she was impatient.
-Me neither.
Wait, so do all of you…
always pour it into a glass?
When it comes to soju, usually, yes.
OH, I SEE
I wonder what WINTER
is looking to eat on the show today.
Let's find out her orders. Show us!
These are WINTER's orders.
Both of them are revealed at once.
Noodle Dish on the Next Level.
Iron Taste to the Max Level.
What does "iron taste" mean?
The taste of metal?
For the first order,
are you looking for a noodle dish?
I love all noodle dishes,
but I always end up eating
something that I'm familiar with.
So today, I wanted to eat
a noodle dish on the next level,
-something very special.
-A new noodle dish.
-Not this level, but the next level.
-The next level.
You all saw her hand flip, right?
She wants something on a new level,
something that can flip her world
and show her a new one.
What's the next one?
Iron Taste to the Max Level?
By Iron Taste to the Max Level,
I mean something very intense,
which I've been hooked on.
So I want to eat something intense,
almost metallic or iron-like.
When I hear "iron taste,"
I'm reminded of the taste
of a pull-up bar.
When I was a kid,
occasionally I'd put my tongue on it.
EYES SHUT
Did you need more iron?
I didn't have enough food!
I thought you had an iron deficiency.
Sung-jun, can you tell us about this?
Let me share my opinion
as a member of MY, aespa's fan club.
What exactly is an iron taste?
Something bold, charismatic,
and exhilarating.
Those are aespa's stylistic concepts.
Yes, their music is often described
as having an "iron taste."
An iron taste, something very intense.
Come to think of it,
shouldn't you jump in, Sung-jun?
-You should.
-You know it.
-You get it.
-Do you want a chance?
-I'll join the round right away.
-Will you?
GLAD
He understands the order perfectly.
-I'll go with Iron Taste.
-Very well.
Sung-jun joins
Iron Taste to the Max Level.
When it comes to an iron taste,
there should be a connection
to the flavor that a knife brings.
-She practically dances with her knife.
-Yes.
I'll show her my magic with an iron taste
that my knife can bring out.
So you're up against Sung-jun?
GLARE, WINCING
-Only the noodle round is available now.
-Noodles.
-Noodle Dish on the Next Level.
-There are many candidates.
RAISING HAND!
SQUEAL♥
OH MY
-WINTER looks so excited.
-You're so happy.
-He wants to be her teacher.
-That's true.
HOPING TO BE WINTER'S TEACHER
"Be my student."
-You're right.
-"The teacher."
Who wants to fight Sam and make noodles?
I'll go.
WELCOME
This is quite hard to do.
The contenders have been decided.
Noodle Dish on the Next Level
just for WINTER.
Let us begin the round
between Sam and Ho-young!
The first round of cook-off
played with WINTER's ingredients.
Chef Jung Ho-young, who's now unable
to cook without Sam, is up.
THE FANS ARE AMUSED
And up against him is Chef Sam Kim,
who now refuses to be his kitchen toolman.
My masters are competing.
You two are currently tied in this season,
both with six wins and six losses,
making the winning rate 50%.
But Chef Sam has recently lost
three times in a row,
whereas Chef Ho-young
has won three consecutive rounds.
-Different momentum levels.
-That's how they're tied now.
On top of that,
in their most recent cook-off,
Chef Ho-young had won.
EP. LEE JUN-YOUNG,
WHEN LIFE HOOKS YOU ON RAMEN
SAM'S BASIL RAMEN
VS. HO-YOUNG'S MERINGUE RAMEN
THE RAMEN ROUND ENDED
IN HO-YOUNG'S VICTORY
Sam had been waiting
to get his revenge since that day.
He has even sharpened his canine
in preparation.
The day of that ramen cook-off
-was the first time I had made ramen.
-Right. That was the case.
But he probably makes ramen every day.
-Right.
-"Every day"?
-So it did feel a little unfair.
-Did it?
If I make pasta today
and beat Sam,
-he won't have anything to complain about.
-He can't complain.
So I will make pasta today.
-Are you making pasta?
-Yes.
That's a big decision.
INHALING
Oh, come on.
What if Sam doesn't make pasta?
That would mean he chickened out.
Yes, it'd mean he's a chicken.
Scared?
I will make pasta.
-Pasta?
-You'll make pasta?
A head-on match.
I'll just win.
Yes, exactly. You can just win.
But the problem is that
aespa currently seems to favor Ho-young,
almost as their fifth member.
-Because I did their dance three times.
-Yeah, sure.
However,
Sam quickly made his case too.
That he also did aespa's dance?
-You did their dance?
-I did.
Ho-young always dances
like it's a routine.
-But I do it only once in a while.
-True.
-Yes, but when was it?
-I did the dance
to "Whiplash"
for Wrap-Wrap-Wrap-Wrap-lash.
YES, RIGHT
Ho-young is the show's KARINA,
-and Sam is the show's WINTER.
-That's the case now.
Before we begin the cook-off,
let me tell you
that the winners of this episode
and the next will get a special prize.
Chef & My Fridge now has
an official premium tableware set.
TA-DA
But only the winners will get it.
ONLY THE WINNERS GET THE PRIZE
WHO'LL WIN THE TABLEWARE SET?
CHEF HO-YOUNG'S INGREDIENTS:
PASTA, BACON, SHRIMP, MILK
CREAM SAUCE, UDON MEAL KIT,
OYSTER SAUCE, PARMESAN, AND MORE
What are you making, Ho-young?
The name of my dish is as follows.
Sam Kim, Beat It, Beat It, Beat It
DISSING HIM WITH A SMILE
HIS DANCE ATTACK IS ON THE NEXT LEVEL
SHOCKED
LAUGHING OUT LOUD
-I see.
-It's called
-Sam Kim, Beat It.
-Beat It.
APPROVED
How is your dish prepared?
I'm going to make cream pasta,
but I want to make it cold.
-Cold cream pasta?
-That's what I'm making.
I'll serve it with your mother's gejang
and let you mix it into the sauce
-when you eat it.
-That sounds good.
That sounds delicious.
If I have enough time,
I saw that you had a mango,
-so I'll serve it with mango bingsu.
-Mango bingsu too?
-Sounds good.
-I'll serve those.
JEALOUS
CHEF SAM'S INGREDIENTS:
BACON, MILK, PARMESAN
POTATO, STRIP LOIN, ENOKI,
CREAM SAUCE, TRUFFLE OIL
What are you making, Chef Sam?
WHAT'S SAM'S NOODLE DISH?
He cleared his throat.
My dish is called…
Su-Su-Su-Super Fresh Pasta
MOVED
THE ORIGINAL
SU-SU-SU-SUPER UDON
THE SHY SUPER FRESH PASTA
HE MUST GIVE IT TO HIM
-He's making fresh pasta.
-Su-Su-Su-Super Fresh Pasta.
He'll make the pasta noodles.
There's the meat filling
that goes into lasagna,
and I'll serve it with pasta.
It will taste like lasagna,
but I'll throw in some potatoes
and make the sauce thicker.
-Everything is better with potatoes.
-I'll do that.
Also, especially for this,
I won't use dried pasta like that.
SUDDENLY ATTACKS HIS INGREDIENT
WHAT'S SO BAD ABOUT MY DRIED PASTA?
-"Dried pasta like that."
-"Like that."
He picked it out for me
and told me it was the best pasta,
-but now he's attacking me.
-I heard it too.
Well, that brand is
one of the best dried pastas.
TRYING TO PATCH IT UP…
But is fresh pasta on the next level?
Completely.
I'll make wide, flat fresh pasta.
-Wide and flat?
-Once you try it,
for fresh noodles made in 15 minutes,
you'll see that it's on another level.
FEELING BITTER
He says fresh pasta is on the next level.
The next level disease.
Are you just making pasta? Anything else?
No, nothing else.
He's confident.
I'll serve only that
simple yet rich-flavored dish.
-Sounds good.
-Just the pasta.
And now,
let us begin the first round for WINTER,
Noodle Dish on the Next Level.
Give us the timer for 15 minutes.
-Whoa.
-Wow.
I love the vibe.
The dancing machine of the show,
HORINA.
-What?
-HORINA.
Chef Jung Ho-young.
The gateway member of the show,
SAMTER.
-SAMTER.
-SAMTER?
-Yes, that's right.
Not WINTER, but SAMTER.
It sounds like Saemteo, fountain,
that literary magazine.
HORINA versus SAMTER.
Which chef will show
the next level of noodle dish?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
LIVE FEED ON
-Wow.
-We can see it like this?
TO KWANGYA!
Starting with salt.
That pasta looked pretty thick.
Is it spaghetti? What is it?
-Everything?
-That much?
-That's too much.
-It is.
They'll stick to one another.
-That's too much.
-It is?
That's a lot.
-That's enough for six.
-Dang it.
-You're breaking it?
-Do that later.
-You're breaking the pasta?
-Later.
Is it okay to push it in like that?
If it's half-immersed
and half out of the pot,
some parts will remain undercooked.
That can happen.
Next, some meat.
-It's bacon.
-Is that bacon?
-Bacon?
-It is.
Cream pasta is often made with bacon.
You have to make a dish on another level.
She has had lots of pasta already.
ON THE PAN
AND IN THE POT
-They're both using bacon.
-They're both using it.
1. COOK BACON AND ONION
They're both using bacon.
NEXT, THE SAUCE!
BUTTER
2. MAKE BÉCHAMEL WITH BUTTER,
FLOUR, MILK, AND PARMESAN
Chef Sam's making béchamel.
Béchamel.
MEANWHILE, HORINA IS…
TOSSING AND TURNING
That pasta is thicker than spaghetti.
-It'll take a while.
-Did you pick this on purpose?
-I didn't.
-I don't think it'll cook in 15 minutes.
-It was intentional.
-It's so thick.
-It's not adequate for cold pasta.
-It's not.
Does she have other pasta?
-I don't think it'll work.
-What now?
-It's too late.
-These are…
They're as thick as clothes hangers.
FOR NOW, THE NEXT STEPS…
-Shrimp and milk.
-Milk.
You're just pouring milk over shrimp?
Yes, I poured it in.
-Is that mustard?
-Mustard?
-No, it's…
-Peanut butter?
-It's pasta sauce.
-Cream sauce.
-It's cream sauce.
-Tsuyu and oyster sauce.
-Tsuyu.
-That has to be good.
-It has to be.
Master, the pasta isn't in the water.
Wait, these are…
It's been 2 minutes and 30 seconds,
yet it's still hard.
It's an emergency.
THE EMERGENCY MAN CLOCKS IN
-He has to overcook it for cold pasta.
-Exactly.
It'll be too hard
if he cooks it like regular spaghetti.
He'll need 14 minutes to cook that.
It could've been a trap.
He must've picked it out intentionally.
-He wants to win that badly.
-That's my master.
Sam, when will you make your pasta?
Me? I'll have to begin now.
-Right after that?
-Yes.
-Potato first.
-Potato.
-So you're adding that to the sauce?
-Yes.
He's using the microwave to cook it.
STRIP LOIN
GRIND
-Is that beef?
-It's beef.
GROUND PEPPER
-They move so quickly.
-Don't they?
The faster you finish your dish,
the more favorable
the impatient WINTER will find you.
If it's too hard to wait,
do you want some tteok?
WANT SOME TTEOK FROM YOUR FRIDGE?
Or ice cream.
-No, she has to enjoy the dishes later.
-She said she hates waiting.
HORINA FEELS RUSHED
KNOWING SHE'LL BE WAITING…
GRATE
That's a lot.
Ho-young, isn't that too much cheese?
It needs a good amount of cheese
to make the sauce thicker and delicious.
Usually,
Chef Sam would've been
grating the cheese for him.
-You're right!
-The help.
-He doesn't have him.
-His "someone" is unavailable.
-No one's there.
-It'd be nice if someone could grate this.
WALKS OVER UNDER A SPELL
-Should I do it?
-Are you free?
I'm not. I have to do it too.
HIS SOMEONE IS ON A STRIKE
THAT SOMEONE IS NOW GONE
Stop taking advantage of him.
WHAT'S SAMTER UP TO AFTER LEAVING HORINA?
FLOUR, ADD EGG
MAKING FRESH PASTA DOUGH!
He's making the pasta dough.
Wow.
HORINA'S BACON IS DONE
You're discarding the bacon fat?
-I'm making cold pasta.
-It's cold.
-He doesn't need it.
-Because it's cold?
What's that?
-I think it's gejang in soy sauce.
-Gejang?
He's separating just the meat
from the marinated crabs.
Will gejang in soy sauce
go well with cream sauce?
-It could be fishy.
-Yes, it can be fishy.
Are you using the meat too?
She'll mix it in later before she eats.
-At the last minute?
-That sounds good.
Only ten minutes left.
You have to make fresh pasta.
Yes, pasta! You have to make pasta!
He's not making pasta yet.
-I have to do it now.
-Now? You have to hurry.
-He just has to flatten it.
-Wait, it looks too wet.
-The dough is too wet.
-It's too wet.
-It's too wet!
-The dough's too wet!
I know because I've made pasta.
It's too wet.
-You're good at pasta.
-I am. It's too wet.
Wet dough is better than dry. It's safer.
-A bit safer.
-It's better to be wet.
That's how he makes pasta.
It may get stuck on the machine.
Unlike the pasta sold at supermarkets…
Is it breaking? Is that okay?
It's okay.
SU-SU-SU-SUPER FRESH PASTA
He's putting lots of work into that pasta.
Hey, the pasta looks nice.
-That took a little longer than I thought.
-It did.
But it cooks faster.
He flattens the pasta once again.
It looks nice and firm.
And he sprinkles some flour.
It looks good.
He's cutting it now.
-Yes, he's cutting the dough.
-It looks nice.
Didn't you say it'd be wider?
-Is that wide?
-Yes.
-It gets bigger as it gets cooked.
-It'll get bigger.
Sam is our go-to guy for pasta.
-That's so cool.
-He uses some more flour.
-It looks similar to mine.
-No.
-It's like Amy's pasta. No?
-What Amy made was jjajangmyeon.
-That's fresh pasta.
-That's fresh pasta?
I should've made it like that.
WHAT ABOUT HORINA,
WHO DOESN'T SPECIALIZE IN PASTA?
ADDING STARCH WATER FOR THICKNESS?
He's cooling the sauce now.
It reminds me of cream udon.
-It seems so.
-It's pasta.
It's udon? It's cream udon.
-It's udon.
-Cream udon is delicious.
It's pasta.
I said it's pasta.
-Cream udon is delicious.
-Yes, I love it.
Nine minutes left.
What will he do with that beef?
I guess he's making ragu
with bacon grease.
-Is that like ragu?
-Yes, but without tomatoes.
STEAMED POTATO, OUT
He's so calm.
4. ADD STEAMED POTATO TO BÉCHAMEL AND BOIL
Is that ice?
ICE IN THE BLENDER?
-What's he grinding with all this noise?
-Ice.
-It's for bingsu, ice flakes.
-He's making bingsu.
RIGHT!
-Mango bingsu.
-Vanilla ice cream.
Have they melted? They're runny.
3. MIX ICE AND VANILLA ICE CREAM
WINTER looks excited.
That's bingsu.
He'll have to finish first
to let her eat it while it's icy.
-Seven minutes left.
-Seven minutes.
-Master, check the pasta.
-Is it okay?
-Dang it. It's like udon.
It'll still be a while.
-It'll be a while.
-Hey, Sam.
-No, it won't work.
-Eight minutes left.
No, it's too firm.
CRUNCH?
Can you throw one to me?
TRY IT
-It's not done.
-It's not?
-Sam did this on purpose.
-Is it an emergency?
It's an emergency.
-What now?
-Is it an emergency?
It'll never cook in five.
CHEWING
It's just like the pasta Amy Park made.
Just heat up some rice
and serve it as soup!
-You should microwave the pasta.
-You have no other choice.
Or ramyeon. Ho-young, use ramyeon noodles.
-It won't cook in five minutes.
-You have to improvise.
Then it won't be pasta anymore.
He can't help it!
It's not going to be done in time.
You have six minutes left.
-It won't be done.
-Ho-young, you're losing your golden time!
No way. It'll never work.
-How bad is it?
-He has no chance.
CHEF SEON-YEOP CHECKS IT TOO
It's way too hard.
It won't work, right? What do you think?
-It won't.
-It won't, right? It's impossible.
I can't even peel the mango.
You have no time to peel the mango!
-Mangoes aren't important now.
-Mango bingsu isn't important.
You're competing with a noodle dish.
It's too hard. It won't be done.
-Does it feel like raw rice?
-Like electric wire.
-Electric wire?
-I feel like I'm chewing on a wire.
The result seems too obvious now.
Man.
-Everything is against Ho-young.
-It's Sam.
This is the best pasta brand.
-He told me to use this.
-He'll lose the noodle dish match.
-Nice texture though.
-He's having trouble peeling mangoes too.
-Has he done it before?
-Why is he so slow?
-It's just hard to peel.
-Sung-ju.
-It's five. Can you check the dishes?
-Yes, let me run over there.
-Oh, no!
-It's a noodle dish match!
Only five minutes remain.
It's already five minutes.
What? Already?
He hasn't done anything yet.
He hasn't. This is really bad!
It's not too late to switch
to ramyeon noodles!
-You have to cool that pasta too.
-It's too hectic.
-It's like that.
-It's tough enough to watch.
So this is the problem, right?
Will you try the pasta?
-Oh, gosh.
-Oh, no.
It's already requiring
quite an effort to pick this up.
It's the thickest spaghetti there is.
-Why did Sam recommend this?
-It's not like that.
It's called chitarra.
-Sam, why did you recommend this?
-It's not like that.
Let me try the pasta
with four minutes remaining.
You don't have to try it.
-Can he beat Sam with that pasta?
-You don't have to.
Is it pasta or wire?
It's a wire.
OH, NO
-Gosh, what now?
-Come on, Sam.
He has four minutes left.
What now?
Everything actually happens.
-It literally does.
-Yes.
FIRST, RETRIEVING THE BINGSU
You have to make a decision.
He's done with the bingsu.
RUSHING
What now? He only has the mango bingsu.
What now?
My heart is racing.
WHAT'S SAMTER UP TO NOW?
5. CHOP OFF THE TOP OF ENOKI
AND COOK IN BUTTER
THE PASTA GARNISH
ADD POTATO BÉCHAMEL
That looks good.
Your pasta will cook in two minutes,
but you still have to hurry.
He's salting the water.
-That looks good.
-Sam begins to cook his pasta.
Chef Ho-young!
Sam has some fresh pasta left, right?
Borrow some.
Yes.
The pasta that someone made.
RUSHING OVER AT THE TEMPTING SUGGESTION
-It's not cooked yet.
-Not yet.
LET ME BORROW SOME PASTA
Hey!
IN MY POT
SAM HAS MADE SOME GOOD NOODLES
LOST HIS PASTA IN A FLASH
SEPARATING WITH A STRAINER
What is this?
He trusted him too much.
-WINTER saw it, so she'll be the judge.
-Yes, she'll be the judge.
GIVING HIM THE REST
-He's too kind.
-The pasta!
HE HAS SUCH A GREAT CHARACTER
He's such a sweet guy.
THIS IS MORE THAN ENOUGH
-Let me try the pasta sauce.
-The sauce is important.
SLURP
Is that pasta good enough
to recover his pride?
My heart is racing.
Is that pasta good enough
to recover his pride?
Sam won.
IT'S THAT GOOD?
I don't even smell anything odd.
It has such a nice and clean taste.
This is really nice.
6. MIX WHITE RAGU PASTA
WITH PARMESAN, OLIVE OIL, AND CREAM SAUCE
DON'T YOU DARE STEP OVER, HORINA
He has to keep emulsifying.
-He made white ragu.
-He did.
HORINA FEELS ANXIOUS…
4. MIX CRAB MEAT WITH SESAME OIL
AND MAKE GEJANG SAUCE
WAS I TOO FOCUSED ON DANCING?
Ho-young faces a crisis.
I trusted him far too much.
BETRAYED BY THE TRUSTED SOMEONE
So I gave you some pasta.
I hope at least
the sauce is good, Ho-young!
The cream sauce!
Is it good enough to beat Sam?
If it is, he'd feel more wronged.
-He has a chance.
-He does?
WHAT A RELIEF
THE CREAM IS ON THE NEXT LEVEL
A minute and 30 seconds!
What a shame, Ho-young.
Oh, no.
-Let me check the first pasta.
-Try it.
I'll check the first pasta.
-It looks done.
-But it has to be cold.
Does it still feel like wire?
-Hey, this might work.
-It might?
-He has a chance?
-He does.
Switch it out!
REMOVES SAM'S PASTA INSTANTLY
-Hurry.
-I'll fish it out.
-Just a little more.
-Thirty seconds.
-Cook it a little longer.
-You got this.
You have a minute. It's okay.
IT'S SO DYNAMIC
Let it cook for 30 more seconds.
-The pasta.
-Give it back to Sam.
Take it back, Sam.
But you took them from me.
You have a chance.
Cook it until the last minute.
I should calm down.
It's cold pasta. You can go second.
You should do the rest.
-Stay calm.
EVERYONE ADDING THEIR TWO CENTS
It's okay, Ho-young. You got this.
-I got this.
-He's making cold pasta.
5. MIX CREAM SAUCE WITH COOKED BACON
-Make use of your time. Thirty seconds.
-Thirty seconds!
HEART POUNDING
SAMTER BEGINS TO PLATE HIS DISH!
That looks so good.
Thirty seconds!
TRUFFLE OIL
Sam's almost done.
And he's done!
SU-SU-SU-SUPER FRESH PASTA IS DONE
He continues to boil the pasta
over high heat.
You have 13 seconds, 12 seconds.
SPIN THE PASTA
Time to pull them out.
-Seven. Six.
-Five. Four.
-Five.
-Three. Two. One.
-That's it. That's time.
-It's over.
-Serve it.
-What a mess. It's okay.
You can plate the food,
but you can't make anything new.
-Wow.
-Wow. That was insane.
My heart is pounding too much.
-That pasta takes the longest to cook.
-It did.
No, it takes 12 minutes.
Twelve minutes?
But he said he'd make cold pasta!
You recommended something that takes
12 minutes for a 15-minute cook-off?
-Did you expect this to happen?
-No.
-Ho-young blurted out a bad word.
-He had to wash it in cold water.
Wait a second.
Are you all siding against me?
Don't you feel bad for Ho-young?
Do you need help?
I think the freezer's broken.
-Is that bingo mangsu?
-Careful.
-Bingo mangsu?
IT'S MANGO BINGSU…
BINGO MANGSU(!)
IT SOUNDS A LOT LIKE BINGSU MANGLED
-That's now called bingo mangsu.
-Bingo mangsu.
That bingo mangsu looks mangled.
MANGSU
EASY LIFE IS NEVER FUN
JUST LIKE GUMMING CHEW OR PEEZE CHIZZA,
IT'S BINGO MANGSU
BUT THE VISUALS…
How come this bingsu has all melted?
MANGLED BINGSU
The freezer was a problem too!
HORINA'S ONE UNLUCKY DAY…
Sound the bell, Ho-young!
He's done too!
-It's like hwachae, fruit salad.
-It's hwachae.
-It's mango hwachae.
-Is that juice?
-It's mango juice.
MOVING WITH EVERYONE'S ATTENTION
-Oh, no. Bingo mangsu.
-Bingo mangsu.
IN THE END, THEY FINISH WITH A HUG
-This will be you soon.
-She can drink it.
It smells so good.
-It does.
-Does it smell delicious?
Both noodle dishes were made
just for WINTER.
WOW♥
Those 15 minutes went by like a storm.
And I don't think we've ever seen
Chef Ho-young look so distraught.
It's been a while.
I think Sam provided the main reason.
I'm telling you, no.
As a fellow Italian chef,
the fact that he recommended
that pasta to make cold pasta
is simply crazy.
What are you saying? That's not the case.
He came to me with that pasta.
-It couldn't have been a mistake.
-He came and asked if it was good.
Then you should've stopped him
from using that one.
I clearly asked him,
"I want to make a cold pasta.
How's this one?"
He said,
"It's great. Make sure you use it."
IT HAS TO BE THIS ONE
-Sam has changed.
-No.
-I'm falsely blamed.
-The losing streak did this to him.
It made him wicked.
Is the bingsu back in the freezer?
I think someone melted the ice cream too.
IT'S JUST NOT HIS DAY…
-Who was it? Who did that?
-That mango bingsu
-must've become bingo mangsu.
-Bingo mangsu.
-Mangsu.
-Now.
Chef Sam was the first to finish.
FRESH PASTA WITH WHITE RAGU SAUCE
CHEF SAM KIM'S SU-SU-SU-SUPER FRESH PASTA
Wow.
-Do I just mix everything?
-Please do.
It looks good.
-I really love rich and creamy sauce.
-I see.
The pasta is rather thick,
so there's lots of sauce on it too.
MMM!
-Must be good.
-It's good.
Is it? I see.
How did he do this in 15 minutes?
Did you use strip loin?
I mixed ground strip loin and bacon stock.
It doesn't have any odd smells,
and the creamy texture
goes very well with the flavor.
-It's so delicious.
-I see.
She has already said that it's delicious
about three to four times.
The noodles are great too.
-I like the chewy texture.
-Yes.
-It's so good.
-It must have a bite to it.
Ho-young should've taken a hint
when Sam said
he was going to make the pasta.
The decision will be made
because of the pasta noodles.
-Competitions can be cold.
-Yes.
He had no choice
if he wanted to win the star.
Ho-young was too naive.
-He was too naive.
-He trusted him.
Is the pasta chewy?
It is.
Something about its texture is really fun,
so I keep craving more.
On top of that, the pasta is fun too.
-It's so good.
-He made it himself, so it must be fun.
-May I keep working on it?
-As you wish.
-Is that okay?
-Do you want to go back and forth?
-I'd love to.
-Really? All right.
-You can leave it there.
-Really?
Do you want some tteok during the switch?
YOU HAVE 20 SECONDS OF WAIT
It's tough to wait. There's ice cream too.
I'M FINE!
Next up, Chef Ho-young's dish.
-Please be cooked.
-Sam Kim, Beat It.
COLD CREAM PASTA
WITH GEJANG IN SOY SAUCE ON THE SIDE
WITH COLD BINGO MANGSU
CHEF JUNG HO-YOUNG'S SAM KIM, BEAT IT
Sam Kim, Beat It.
-Whoa.
-Beat It.
She'll find out
if the noodles are fully cooked.
It wasn't so bad
by the time I tried it toward the end.
I'm dying to find out.
It was somewhat edible by then.
I do like my noodles a bit undercooked.
Really? I see.
This pasta was served cold.
It's my first time trying cold pasta.
-The noodles…
-It won't roll up.
-A cold cream pasta.
-The pasta won't roll up.
-Is it still a wire?
-It seems like it.
If so, you can't roll it up.
Oh, but you did.
-So with the crab?
-First,
try it as is,
and then try it with some crab.
FIRST, THE PASTA ALONE
CHUCKLE
-She chuckled.
-Is it undercooked?
WEE WOO WEE WOO
Hey. Turn that thing off.
-It's an emergency.
-The pasta isn't fully cooked, right?
It could get stuck between your teeth.
-It could be way too good.
-That?
-Next, with the crab?
-Yes, mix it in.
That's the gejang in soy sauce
that her mother sent her.
She ends up eating it like this.
-I wonder what that mix is like.
-Right?
-I wonder what it's like.
-It'd go really well together.
-It looks good.
-Mmm!
-Huh?
Mmm!
-You look surprised.
-They go so well together.
They go very well?
We didn't expect that.
I've never had anything like it.
-The next level?
-It goes perfectly with the order.
-It's an emergency for Sam.
-An emergency.
-Emergency.
-It suits the order better.
He could've won
if the pasta was fully cooked.
-The pasta, right?
-Huh? Maybe not.
-No?
-Have you had it before?
It somehow tastes like bulgogi.
-Bulgogi?
-It tastes like a bulgogi burger!
A bulgogi burger?
Why does that taste like a bulgogi burger?
She had good sesame oil,
so I added a drop into the crab.
-That was why.
-Like teriyaki sauce.
The pasta wasn't heavily seasoned.
I think he considered
adding the crab meat.
I added the savory flavor
with grated cheese.
-Is it good?
-Yes.
Is the pasta cooked well?
The pasta's evenly…
It's evenly a bit…
-Evenly undercooked.
-It must be evenly undercooked.
-Stop eating it, then.
-Evenly undercooked.
It's evenly undercooked.
-But it's fine by me.
-Is it?
It's not so bad for my taste.
Was this intentional?
Yes, she seemed to be
quite impatient,
so I wanted her to chew it well.
-Because she's impatient,
-To slow her down.
…she probably has had undercooked pasta.
GLANCING
-Let me try that again.
-Going back.
-She's now…
-It must be hard.
-Thank you.
-She likes to take her time with meals,
switching between the dishes.
-After all, the order is the Next Level.
-Right.
YUM
WINTER is putting a lot of emphasis
on how it must be on the next level.
Mmm.
The pasta noodles are really delicious.
GLANCING
That's hard to beat.
-I'm torn.
-You are?
-I still have bingsu.
-Yes.
-Bingsu.
-Yes, right!
Is it really bingsu?
-He's bringing it now.
-Bingo mangsu.
-It has to be delicious.
-Bring her the bingo mangsu.
-Wait.
It melted more in the freezer.
What kind of freezer is that?
-Is that juice?
-Oh, no.
RUNNY…
It's so runny.
Some say that Sam Kim
has cut the power to the freezer.
A RATHER VICIOUS RUMOR
-I knew it.
-This vicious rumor is going around.
SLOSHING
He's like, "Go down, Ho-young."
It's hwachae.
-How funny.
-It's actually mango hwachae.
-Mango hwachae?
-You want that in summer.
-I added cherries too.
-You called it bingsu.
-It's hwachae.
-How is it suddenly hwachae?
You're right.
Wait, this is just liquid.
It's liquid, right?
SLURRRP
She's drinking it.
Is it bingsu or mangled bingsu?
SMACK SMACK
MMM
It's something
you can get anywhere, right?
PFFT!
The usual mango bingsu
you can now get just about anywhere.
Vanilla ice cream.
IT'S JUST ICE CREAM
The ice cream flavor?
-The ice cream flavor. Right?
-All he did was blend ice cream with ice.
-It should've been like bingsu.
-It's now like…
MMM
It just tastes like
-regular mango bingsu.
-It's just mango and ice cream.
-But it's good. Delicious.
-But it's good.
That wasn't the main dish.
-It wasn't.
-What a shame.
-This is hard.
-She likes this, so it's like a bonus.
-Let's see KARINA try it while she thinks.
-Yes, some for KARINA.
Please try Chef Sam's dish first.
Thank you for the food.
A BIG BITE
Mmm!
Mmm.
-Mmm.
-She's excited.
What does that look mean?
Wait, what's going on?
-It's so delicious.
-Is it really?
It's Sam's pasta.
-This fresh pasta is…
-Different, right?
Yes, it's a stroke of genius.
I also love this subtle truffle aroma.
I'm not so good with truffles,
but this is delicious.
A BIG BITE
YUM
MMM
She's eating again.
WINTER'S ON A MARATHON
-The next one.
-I'm looking forward…
-…to this one.
-Chef Ho-young's dish,
Sam Kim, Beat It.
We have some more of his dish,
so please try some.
How different is it from the fresh pasta?
THE RIGHT-HAND CHEFS JOIN THEM
SLOW, LONG-DISTANCE EATING
KARINA TAKES A BITE TOO
-Why? What is it? Is it cooked?
-It's good.
-Is it okay?
-I see.
-Is it evenly cooked?
KARINA says it's cooked well.
-Some time passed, so it's a bit soggier.
-Is that so?
WINTER CHECKS AGAIN
It could've become soggier
while WINTER tried some.
-It's good.
-Yes, it's good.
We can call this al dente
and say that some will like it.
-Let me try it with the gejang.
-She's adding the crab this time.
YUM-YUM
-It must be so flavorful.
-Cream sauce and soy sauce.
MMM
MMM!
I'm sorry, but tell us
instead of sending signals.
-What are you two doing?
-You're sending signals to each other.
When I had it with gejang,
-the flavor changed 4 times in my mouth.
-It changed 4 times?
First, it tasted like cream,
then soy sauce,
then they mix
into a blend of creamy soy sauce,
and lastly, like a bulgogi burger.
THAT'S WHAT WINTER SAID♥
-Just like what WINTER said.
-Yes.
The right-hand chefs,
have you tried it too?
-Yes.
-What did you think?
They actually made it happen.
I thought it wouldn't come together.
I see. How did it taste?
It also came out very delicious.
Add more details
and tell them why it was good.
IMMEDIATELY DISCIPLINED
My gosh.
Can you do this
in the next episode, Chef Do-hee?
-I'll try to pull something off.
-You'll try.
-He's rather frightened.
-He is?
He has now seen the 15 minutes.
Time flew by too quickly.
-It does, right?
-It flew by.
There's a subtle smell of truffle,
and the mix of gejang in soy sauce,
truffle, and cream sauce
seemed unlikely at first,
but they work well as a team.
CONTINUES TO EAT UNTIL THE END
Even as we chatted,
WINTER continued to eat her food.
Have you made a decision?
-I think so.
-She made her decision.
The chef who gets chosen by WINTER
will take both the star
and the tableware set.
Also, we'll give the winning chef
another chance to do his dance.
So who's the winner?
Press one for Sam Kim.
Press two for Jung Ho-young.
If you made your decision,
please press the button.
Right now.
-I did.
-You did?
She made her decision.
Let's find out WINTER's choice.
Show us! Which one is it?
Noodle Dish on the Next Level.
Ho-young has won three times in a row,
and Sam has lost three times in a row.
Will Ho-young keep his winning streak?
Or will Sam break his losing streak?
Noodle Dish on the Next Level!
Who did WINTER choose?
-Next Level!
Who is it?
SAM KIM WINS
SU-SU-SU-SUPER FRESH PASTA WINS
Sam wins.
THE FRESH PASTA WINS
That was awful, Chef Sam.
-Your plan worked.
-In the end, his plan worked.
-It did.
-It went according to plan.
If you rewind the tapes and check
the moment he picked up the pasta,
I recommended that he use it.
FINALLY ADMITS
He's scary.
Sam had been painting this big picture.
How long do I cook this for?
Let me see. Give it to me.
I don't see it written anywhere.
This is the best pasta.
This is the top pasta brand.
GETTING CHILLS…
I told you so.
Also, the heat was too weak
when he cooked the pasta.
-I see.
-Because pasta is cooked over high heat.
-You knew that?
-Why didn't you tell him?
-You were just watching?
-It was boiling right here.
-You should've told him to use high heat.
-He already knew.
-I thought he had a plan, so I didn't…
-That's awful!
What? What do you mean?
Sam is such a scary guy now!
-These stars don't mean that much.
-They don't.
Just let me win for once, okay?
SHARING HIS SORROW
"Let me win for once."
You have to understand that.
-Yes.
-Could've been his fourth loss in a row.
A four game losing streak is a bit sad.
You lost against him last time.
-Also, he's the pasta expert here.
-The game was already over.
Was there a particular reason?
The fresh noodles were so delicious
that the dish felt like
it was on another level,
-just like what I ordered.
-It was different.
What about the mangsu?
-Mangsu?
-Mangled bingsu, right?
-It's mangsu.
-It's still in a liquid form.
-It flooded over.
-It was also delicious.
-It's overflowing.
Does this mean Sam is now the new teacher?
Huh?
WHICH TEACHER CAPTURED YOU?
-Is Sung-jun gone?
-Not yet.
I'll decide after I try his dish later.
WINTER IS SLOWLY SHAKEN
Let me dare to say that.
She'll decide after tasting his food.
Please put a star on Sam's chest.
This is his seventh win!
-Congratulations.
-Right here.
-Put it above his name tag.
-Thank you for the food.
And the tableware.
Please take the tableware set.
It looks so cool.
Now, put that down and dance with her.
Dance with WINTER. One, two, three, four.
Su-Su-Su-Super Fresh Pasta
Congratulations!
-Thank you.
SU-SU-SU-SUPER…
The second cook-off
with ingredients from WINTER's fridge.
Witch With a Wok, aka Yi Moon-jung,
who has been disciplining the show,
versus Chef Kwon Sung-jun,
who'll beg WINTER if he must
to escape this crisis.
IRON TASTE TO THE MAX LEVEL
Ever since Moon-jung
made her first appearance on the show,
-she has never lost.
-Wow.
-She's on the rise with a 100% win rate.
-So cool.
She has waited for a day like this
since the day she set foot in here.
-What is it?
-She'll be facing…
-…the winner of CCW.
-You're right!
-She has always wanted to do that.
-Right.
She has waited for the day
she'll get to challenge Sung-jun.
After all,
he bears the honor of first place on CCW,
-so he won't be an easy fight.
-No.
I will cook today with the intention
-of learning from him.
-She's so cool.
-She's here to learn.
-Currently,
Chef Sung-jun has become third place,
thanks to his five-win streak.
CURRENTLY 3RD PLACE,
TIED WITH HYUN-SUK AND HO-YOUNG
For Sung-jun, today is
the biggest test he'll have to pass.
-Yes.
-Idol stars never gave him a star.
ALWAYS LOST WITH AN IDOL STAR GUEST
-That's his weakest point.
-The weakest point.
After all, WINTER
is my beloved student.
I've already cooked for her,
so I already know very well
what she likes to eat.
I have a feeling
that I might have an advantage.
And you said this too.
"Unlike
Eun-yeong and Poong who failed,
I will step up and keep the pride
of the OG chefs of the show."
You said all kinds of stuff.
LET ME KEEP THE SHOW'S PRIDE
The authentic Chinese chef,
Eun-yeong, got destroyed miserably.
And then, the bootleg chef, Poong,
also got destroyed.
As another authentic Chinese chef,
I will do my best to stop her.
How are you an authentic Chinese chef?
-Who do you think you are?
-I am
certified in Chinese cuisine,
authenticated by the state.
AN AUTHENTIC CHEF APPROVED BY THE STATE?
-Are you certified?
-What?
-Are you certified? I knew it.
-I am.
She's certified as a master craftsman.
-A master craftsman?
-You're a master craftsman?
Have you been to Hong Kong?
Hong Kong?
I consider it my second hometown,
so just last year,
I went there four times.
Isn't Jong-won the second hometown guy?
I also plan to visit there
twice more this year.
Wasn't Naples your second hometown?
-It's my first hometown.
-The first hometown.
-What about Korea then?
-Have you abandoned Korea?
-You're not Korean?
-Where are you from?
Korea is my 0.5th hometown.
KOREA IS… HIS 0.5TH HOMETOWN
He just straight up talks nonsense now.
In this round,
KARINA will join Jung-hwan
for the five-minute check.
-I feel ready.
-You are?
If it's any good…
HAHA♥
I'LL RESPOND WITH THE SEAL CLAP
CHEF SUNG-JUN'S INGREDIENTS:
RICE PAPER, STRIP LOIN, PORK NECK
SAUSAGE, SHRIMP, TOFU, BOK CHOY,
KING OYSTER MUSHROOM, AND MORE
What are you going to make, Chef Sung-jun?
The dish I prepared today is
Tasty-Lash, T-T-T-Tasty-Lash
-Oh my.
-Tasty-Lash, T-T-T-Tasty-Lash
THIS DANCE IS…
Tasty-Lash, T-T-T-Tasty-Lash
FLAPPING
FLAPPING WITH HIS SHORT LIMBS
MIRROR THERAPY
AFTER SU-SU-SU-SUPER FRESH PASTA!
THE LEGS ARE SHORT TOO
REFUSING TO WATCH
She's embarrassed.
HIS DANCE IS EMBARRASSING TO WATCH…
He does have shorter arms.
LAUGHING
How will you make T-T-T-Tasty-Lash?
First of all, I am using mala.
Then I'll make mapo tofu
with a twist of Italian
and make pasta with tofu.
-Whoa.
I'll also make mala cream shrimp dim sum
-and serve those too.
-Dim sum?
I'll use rice paper
to make a dim sum called the lion's head.
That's my plan.
He'll make it spiky.
The key to my dish is the fact
that I wanted WINTER
to protect her stomach
before she eats spicy food.
So I'll serve food like cream or tofu
to keep her stomach free from pain.
I even considered that part.
How kind of him.
She can't usually eat spicy food.
-I'll control myself.
-Okay.
CHEF MOON-JUNG'S INGREDIENTS:
RICE PAPER, SCALLOP, SHRIMP
PORK NECK, MANGO, LETTUCE,
CABBAGE, BOK CHOI, CARROT, AND MORE
Up against him is Chef Moon-jung.
What are you making?
Sung-jun.
-No Mala Acting Up!
-Whoa, what?
Sung-jun, No Mala Acting Up!
That was so scary.
WINTER said she likes mala xiang guo…
-Mala xiang guo.
-Mala xiang guo?
-I thought you were swearing.
No mala talking.
SHUTS…
Say goodbye to ordinary mala xiang guo.
I'll prepare mala tacos.
-Mala tacos?
-Sounds good.
-And
the key to making good tacos
is the tortilla.
-"Tortilla."
-Yar?
I'll use rice paper.
-With rice paper?
-Yes.
I'll make tortillas with rice paper
and turn them into mala tacos.
The moment you take a bite,
you'll wonder if you're in Mexico,
or China.
Are you in Mexico or China?
-That kind of taste.
-Yes.
WHAT'S THAT KIND OF TASTE?
I feel like I'm watching a musical.
Or a comedy sketch contest.
I've seen that on a comedy skit.
WINTER, once you have
my mala tacos,
you won't be able to help any mala
but give me the star!
I'm rarely scared of people,
but that girl is scary.
T-T-T-Tasty-Lash
versus Kwon Sung-jun, No Mala Acting Up!
Let us begin the cook-off now.
Ready to show him
how the witch uses her knife,
the undefeated Chef Yi Moon-jung!
Ready to show the spice level
as the winner of CCW,
the chef with five consecutive wins,
Chef Kwon Sung-jun.
Who'll surprise WINTER
with a more intense iron taste?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
TO KWANGYA, GAME IN!
Begin!
THE WITCH STARTS WITH HER KNIFE
GREEN ONION
I've never heard of mala tacos.
Why did you throw that in?
-To check the temperature.
-The temperature.
POTATO CHIPS
DETERMINATION ON THE MAX LEVEL!
CULTURE SHOCK
The magic wand!
BEGINS THE ROUND
WITH AN IRON TASTE PERFORMANCE
Some people on our forum are saying
that she isn't Witch With a Wok,
but probably Shaman With a Wok
or something like that.
Ho-young, can you cut the rice paper?
-Cut these?
-Yes. Please help me.
LET'S SEE…
SLOW
The battle to find the "iron taste."
RED PEPPER POWDER
CHILI OIL
MADE BY AN AUTHENTIC CHINESE CHEF!
A SLOTH CUTTING RICE PAPER
ALIGNING…
SNIP
THE SPEEDY GUY MOVES FASTER!
1. POUR HOT OIL OVER GARLIC,
RED PEPPER POWDER, AND GREEN ONION
Huh?
There they are. The ones she mentioned,
tortilla.
Tortilla.
-Those are usually for spring rolls.
-Yes.
ABRACADABRA
STICK TOGETHER!
She attached two sheets together.
She's trying to glue
rice paper together to make tortillas.
-It won't stick.
-It won't.
It happens in no time with hot water,
but it takes time with cold water.
I hope she didn't
just think of this in her head.
Just soak it completely in water.
That'll work better.
-Shh.
-Okay.
It's taking over a minute
just to stick rice paper together!
2. GLUE TWO RICE PAPER PIECES WITH WATER
BACK TO THE SPEEDY GUY!
ONION
2. COOK ONION AND GREEN ONION IN OLIVE OIL
AND GET THE BLENDER READY!
He's mixing beef with pork neck.
-Beef and pork neck.
-Is it strip loin and pork?
-Yes.
HE'S THINKING OF MAKING RAGU!
SAUSAGE
REMOVING THE CASE!
KING OYSTER MUSHROOM
3. GRIND STRIP LOIN AND PORK NECK,
COOK WITH SAUSAGE, KING OYSTER MUSHROOM
Wait, chips?
-Looks good.
-Chips?
-She's using potato chips.
-You're using those?
For the crunchy texture.
It's to add the crunchy texture?
That's why it's not just tortilla,
but tortilla with the R trill.
LAUGH AT THE GRANDPA'S JOKE
GOOD GIRL
But it mostly comes off.
-It should stick to it, right?
-Yes.
-Shouldn't it be sticking?
-Yes. But it's not working.
-It's taking quite a while.
-It is.
-Oh, no.
-She spent over two minutes on that.
You spent two minutes.
NO MALA WORRYING
-It's the most important step.
-It's the most important.
-Is everything planned?
-Of course.
It's such a wonder.
Tomato sauce and oyster sauce.
He's mixing all these sauces
to make his "iron taste."
-It's so red.
-And now,
he begins to bring out the iron flavors.
It's a fire show.
Sung-jun looks like a Chinese chef
as he works with that wok.
Hong Kong must be your second hometown.
It is!
Da ge hao!
DA GE HAO?
Da ge hao means, "You're great, my man."
Not dajia hao, but da ge hao?
I think he's appreciating
the fact that I'm cutting these.
DA GE HAO: GREETINGS, OLDER BROTHER
Green onion.
SLICE
This is how
the authentic Chinese chef chops!
She's very fast!
MOUTH-DROPPING
Look at Moon-jung go.
They were both shocked.
Mala sauce, red pepper powder,
cooking wine, oyster sauce,
arrabbiata,
ground pepper, plum extract, and vinegar.
Their sauces look similar.
They're both similarly colored
after using mala sauce.
The difference is the tomato sauce.
What's Sung-jun up to?
-He's using a cookie cutter on tofu.
-He said he'd make pasta with it.
-Yes.
-By making holes.
-Like rigatoni?
-I get it.
-Right.
-I see.
-Should've made the smaller hole first.
-Right?
Say it louder for him.
Tell him that.
-That's his pasta?
-It's an emergency.
-It's too soft.
-Can that turn into pasta?
-He'll fry those.
Shouldn't he make the hole
after deep-frying it then?
-It'd be too tough to penetrate.
-It's too limp now.
I think it'll come undone
when it goes into the oil.
It'll probably rise.
I think it'll get mashed.
Right? What he's doing
doesn't look quite right.
READY FOR ANOTHER SPELL
She pours oil on top of the paper.
-That stick is useful!
-She's trying to make taco shells.
That was why she needed the stick.
It's bent in the stick's shape.
BECOMING GOLDEN BROWN!
It's curved.
-Wow.
-That's good.
-It seems to be working.
Something smells burning.
Something's burning.
DONE WITH ONE FOR NOW
-I just spilled some oil.
-It's burnt.
-It's an emergency.
-It's not.
No more acting up.
-"No more acting up."
THE BLACK MAMA'S TACOS
ARE COMING ALONG NICELY
It's the oil.
That black smoke
kind of suits Witch With a Wok.
-It suits her.
-It does, right?
Those look great.
WHAT ABOUT TOFU RIGATONI?
-He made them.
-He did.
THESE LOOK GREAT TOO
It looks so detailed. Is that tofu?
-Tofu rigatoni.
-He made awesome shapes with tofu.
SHOWING OFF
He's so relaxed.
WINTER's keeping a close eye on him.
Should she just keep him as her teacher?
Not everyone can be a teacher.
SHRIMP
STARCH
He drops oyster sauce into the blender.
He's grinding shrimp and pork neck.
-Shrimp and pork neck again?
-Yes.
It's probably the filling
for the mala dim sum.
The filling for mala dim sum.
What are you doing, Ho-young?
I'm making the skin for mala dim sum.
-You are?
-Yes.
-For the dim sum?
-Is the rice paper ready?
-Not yet?
-He's urging Ho-young.
It's an emergency.
Wait.
WHY?
I DECIDE WHEN IT GETS DONE
This is a new way of dealing with him.
Why should I care?
SEAL CLAPS
-He's in a foul mood from losing.
-Right?
-He made me do this after I lost to Sam.
-How can he be in a good mood?
PROUD
Sung-jun doesn't seem to have enough time.
It's an emergency.
-Eight minutes left.
-It's an emergency.
-Eight minutes.
-You're up in three minutes.
3 MINUTES UNTIL THE INTERIM CHECK
THE WITCH BEGINS TO CHOP TOO!
ONION
There she goes.
-Whoa.
Whoa.
SPREAD OUT
She's so fast.
CHEONGYANG PEPPER
CABBAGE
BOK CHOY
I love that sound.
HER CHOPPING SKILLS ARE ON THE NEXT LEVEL!
She can save a lot of time
because she's quick with her hands.
You're right.
Her biggest strength
is that her hands are very nimble.
That means she can save a lot of time.
She's so fast.
-It seems to have a big impact.
-It does.
It's an emergency. I forgot.
-What? Forgot what?
-Forgot what?
What did you forget?
-Using this tofu.
-The tofu?
Zero waste.
DROPPING TOFU INTO MILK!
IN A SOLO TOFU HELL!
Well, tofu cooks quickly.
-He's making sauce.
-He just added butter. Is that milk?
Butter in milk?
-It's milk.
-Tofu?
I think he's making tofu cream sauce.
-His dish seems complicated.
-It does.
Bok choy.
-Fen haozi noodles.
-Fen haozi.
He adds fen haozi too.
Wow.
He said he'd make dim sum.
-He did.
-It looks good.
Emergency. Running out of time.
He added cheese too.
BLEND IT TO MAKE TOFU CREAM SAUCE
TRUFFLE CREAM SAUCE
THIS TIME, MALA CREAM SAUCE!
MALA SAUCE!
That looks like lava.
10. MIX AND BOIL MILK,
TRUFFLE CREAM, GARLIC, AND MALA SAUCE
-Here.
-Thank you!
DIM SUM SKIN IS READY TOO!
WATER
Why is he spraying that?
-Five minutes left.
-Five minutes left!
Jung-hwan and KARINA!
-My turn.
-Let's go.
-Please check the kitchen!
-Taste the food with these.
Okay.
Whoa.
I get to come to the kitchen?
Who'll create a better iron taste?
Chef Moon-jung is busy too.
-What's she doing? Which cut is that?
-Pork neck.
-She's cooking pork neck.
6. COOK PORK NECK, SCALLOP, SHRIMP,
AND VEGGIES IN MALA OIL SAUCE
These are ready. Don't they look great?
-They look nice.
-They do.
-They turned out well.
-How insane.
AND A FIRE SHOW!
She's adding the smoky flavor.
Yes, I'm adding the smoky flavor.
-Is that the filling?
-Yes, it's the taco filling.
-Why don't we taste the taco filling?
-The taco filling!
-KARINA. One second. She's not done.
-I'm not done yet. One sec.
-Visit that side first.
-Visit the other side.
She refused us.
-The tofu rigatoni looks good!
-Try the sauce.
This one? What's this sauce?
-It's ragu. Mapo ragu.
-Mapo ragu.
Why don't you try this?
-I'll try it.
-Mapo ragu.
-KARINA gets her first taste!
-The ragu!
-It's good!
Is it good enough to make a seal clap?
It's delicious!
CLAPPING
THE SEAL CLAP IS SUCH A USEFUL TRICK
GREAT JOB, KARINA!
That sauce needs to be good.
But it doesn't taste Chinese.
-I guess the mapo sauce wasn't it.
-Try some.
-Is it Italian?
-It's Italian Chinese.
-He mixed Italian and Chinese.
-Try some, Jung-hwan.
He's not good with spicy food, though.
Jung-hwan, is it worthy of the seal clap?
It's worthy of the seal clap!
-I personally think it tastes Chinese.
-I guess it's authentic.
I tasted more tomato sauce.
It has the tomato flavor,
but I could taste more spiciness.
-It's delicious.
-It's quite spicy.
Do you think WINTER can take this?
It's spicy.
She can totally eat this one.
It's right at her limit.
-It's a bit spicy for me.
-I see.
I'm not good with spicy food.
The mala dim sum just got dropped in.
COOLING THE TACO FILLING
Because she has to put them in the tacos.
Can we try this?
-Sure.
-It's the taco filling, right?
-KARINA.
-Try some.
Does that also make you do the seal clap?
Dajia hao.
Xiexie!
ADDING LETTUCE TO TORTILLA
Let me try a bite too.
THE HOST TAKES A BITE TOO
She added more veggies.
This one's a bit more…
That one is spicier,
while this one is a bit more sugary.
Spicy and sour.
-It's delicious, hao chi.
-Hao chi.
If both dishes are spicy,
whoever finishes first
will have the advantage.
Chef Moon-jung has to finish first
no matter what happens.
-She has to?
-Otherwise, it'll taste bland.
-Please hurry, Chef Moon-jung.
-You'll have to hurry up.
-Emergency.
-What's that sauce?
-This? Mala cream sauce.
-Mala cream sauce.
You have less than two minutes.
-A minute and 40 seconds.
MANGO
REMOVING THE SEED
BY CUTTING IT HORIZONTALLY
AND REMOVES THE SKIN AT ONCE!
-She's so fast.
-It looks similar.
Witch With a Wok.
-Try the mala cream sauce.
-Mango?
DICED CUCUMBER, ONION, MANGO!
-What's that?
-Veggie fritter?
-The lion's head.
-Lion's head.
-This is what the dim sum looks like.
PLATING THE DISH!
FIRST, MALA CREAM SAUCE
VINEGAR
7. MIX VINEGAR, OLIVE OIL, GROUND PEPPER
-Can you mix this?
-I'll do it.
-One minute left.
-One minute!
-You have to fill the tacos now!
-Moon-jung should finish first!
Fill the taco shells!
-Down to the last minute.
-Fifty seconds.
Even Poong is helping her.
He's plating his dish right now.
-I love the color.
-Lion's head.
-That's probably mala sauce.
-Looks Chinese.
WHAT ABOUT MAPO TOFU?
-Forty seconds.
-Wait.
-Wait?
-Wait. It's this one.
-It's almost…
-What's that?
-The cream sauce?
-He must be confused.
-There are too many sauces.
-He got them confused.
-He has three different sauces.
-Thirty seconds.
-Thirty seconds left.
I'm done.
Do you see some foam?
-It has to foam?
-Can you add this?
-Mix this and this? Pour it in?
-Together.
-Pour this in?
-That's mango salsa.
-Twenty seconds.
-Mango salsa.
TOFU CREAM SAUCE WITH TOFU RIGATONI
TOPPED WITH MAPO RAGU SAUCE!
Are you done? Put it in a bowl.
-A bowl? Where?
-Ten. Nine.
-Eight.
-Seven. Six.
THE SPEED OF LIGHT!
-Four. Three.
GREEN ONION
-Five. Four.
-Three. Two.
-One.
-Moon-jung finishes first.
Yi Moon-jung is done.
That's time.
-Sung-jun, did you just make two dishes?
-Yes.
Ring the bell. He's done.
Both chefs are done.
SCARED
They both have nice shapes.
RETURNING TO THE REAL WORLD!
MISSION COMPLETE!
Whoa, KARINA.
I think you'll love it.
-Really?
-Yes.
All dishes are finished
for WINTER's order,
Iron Taste to the Max Level.
Chef Moon-jung's dish,
Kwon Sung-jun, No Mala Acting Up!
-That was your dish name?
-Yes.
FIERY MALA TACO FILLING
INSIDE THE MAGICAL TORTILLA
MANGO SALSA TO ADD
A REFRESHING-IRON FLAVOR
CHEF YI MOON-JUNG'S
KWON SUNG-JUN, NO MALA ACTING UP!
Thank you.
They really look like tacos.
-Whoa.
Top it with mango salsa and take a bite.
Thank you.
-Add lots. Yes.
-Lots?
LOTS
IT LOOKS TOO BIG FOR HER MOUTH
-Bite on it.
-Bite on it?
THAT'S TRUE
She can't exactly suck on it.
She'll have to bite it.
-It's something you eat with your hand.
-It's too big.
CRUNCH
It sounds crunchy.
-My gosh.
-What's it like? I can hear the crunch.
Mmm.
-Mmm!
-Did you get everything?
I wonder if that tastes like tortilla.
It tastes a bit more
intense than I thought.
But at the same time, it tastes fresh.
-That's the mango salsa.
-Yes, I think that's it.
It has that crunchiness
and the refreshing flavor inside.
What's in here? Mango and what?
Mango, onion, and cucumber.
Let me go for this side.
GOING FOR THE OTHER SIDE
Was it impossible to make it smaller?
You can crush it.
-Lettuce will keep the filling in.
-Crush the side…
-…and flatten it.
-Flatten it a little.
-She can just break it?
-It doesn't matter.
It must be fun to flatten that.
TAKING A MUCH EASIER BITE
You're right.
VERY JEALOUS
MMM!
I hope the flavors work together.
Scallops!
It's delicious.
Yes.
I made it with scallops,
shrimps, and pork.
Scallops, shrimps, and pork?
The ingredients for mala xiang guo
turned into taco fillings.
-"Xiang guo."
-"Mala xiang guo."
Is that how they say it in China?
"Mala xiang guo."
-It's how I say it.
-Just you?
It must be the sound she uses often.
That and some more.
It seems a bit difficult to eat.
-It seems hard.
-It's quite…
-What's it like?
-It's not just intense.
-It's refreshing and cleanly intense.
-Is that so?
It's not the spiciness
that adds the intensity.
The sauce and everything
has an intensity in itself.
It's not just plainly spicy.
May I add a word?
-Sure.
-I intentionally made it less intense,
so it won't hurt your stomach
while you're working.
WINTER'S STOMACH PROTECTOR
That was something Sung-jun said.
-I wanted to make a healthy dish.
-I see.
-Next, he made two dishes.
-Two dishes.
T-T-T-Tasty-Lash.
MALA MAPO TOFU DISGUISED AS PASTA
MALA SHRIMP DIM SUM
THAT'LL GIVE OFF AN IRON TASTE
CHEF KWON SUNG-JUN'S T-T-T-TASTY-LASH
That's a lot of food.
-So that one is…
-Mapo tofu
reinterpreted as rigatoni.
The sauce on top was spicy, right?
-To me, yes. Right?
-It was.
-Did you try this sauce?
-That's the spicy one.
But I think you'll be fine.
-I'll eat it together.
-Use a spoon and grab everything.
Everything.
There's cream sauce underneath.
-It'll help with the spiciness.
-Looks good.
Mmm.
Hmm?
-I don't find it spicy.
-I see.
Does the cream sauce help?
It really does.
They integrate quite nicely.
-It's not too intense.
-I see.
It's not that spicy.
-The cream sauce must help.
-Eat it with lots of sauce.
-It's definitely intense.
-Isn't it?
The iron taste.
REALLY BROUGHT OUT THE FLAVOR
-This is tofu, right?
-It's tofu.
But it also has a chewy texture.
-Yes, I coated it with potato starch.
-Potato starch.
And I added some fen haozi too.
-Fen haozi?
-Yes, to add texture.
ANOTHER BITE
I thought it'd be crunchy
because he deep-fried it,
-but I think fen haozi makes it chewy.
-The chewy texture.
It's good.
HEHE♥
-He made one more dish.
-Yes. Whoa.
That's mala cream shrimp dim sum.
You just got the iron taste
of the dish's spiciness.
Now you'll get to the bulk
of the iron taste.
It totally smells like mala.
Yes, he deep-fried it.
WHAT'S THE SHRIMP DIM SUM LIKE?
AGAIN, SENDING A SIGNAL FIRST
-This is definitely Chinese food.
-It is?
It's totally that mala flavor.
It's truly intense.
It's mala shrimp itself.
A SERIES OF INTENSE MALA FLAVORS
-I've never had anything like it.
-You've never had it?
I'm curious.
-It's so good.
-Trying it separately.
How am I going to pick one?
-She's now worried.
-Please.
-They're so different.
-They are?
These are simply very intense,
whereas this one is intense,
yet it also has
the clean and refreshing flavors too.
-It was Iron Taste to the Max Level.
-Iron Taste to the Max Level.
WHICH DISH HAD A STRONGER IRON TASTE?
-KARINA, do you want to try it?
-Do you?
Let's hear from KARINA.
CRUNCH
Mmm!
MAKING A CONNECTION
I feel like I'm in China,
doing yoga.
Doing yoga in China?
She's my kind.
-Doing yoga in China?
-It's definitely China,
but I'm looking after my health,
trying to keep up with my wellness.
So no Mexico?
It's like a Mexican person
doing yoga in China.
A Mexican person doing yoga in China?
-Yes, doing yoga.
-Doing yoga.
I completely get it.
Next, Chef Sung-jun's dish,
T-T-T-Tasty-Lash.
That's the shrimp dim sum.
The sauce alone was spicy,
but the cream must balance it out.
Yes, the cream sauce that's underneath.
These are definitely China China.
-Definitely?
-Da ge hao.
-"China China."
The intensity comes in levels.
It'd be nice
if we had these three as a set.
I love this mix.
THE MOMENT OF TRUTH
You must choose now.
-What do I do?
-It's that time.
Press one to pick Moon-jung,
and two for Sung-jun.
Make your decision
and press the button.
-I did.
-You did?
Which chef did WINTER side with?
Let's find out the result. Show us!
Iron Taste to the Max Level.
If Sung-jun wins,
this will be his sixth straight win.
It'll be six wins in a row.
If Moon-jung wins,
she'll remain unbeaten with the third win.
Which one did WINTER choose?
-Who's the winner?
The winner is?
YI MOON-JUNG WINS
KWON SUNG-JUN, NO MALA ACTING UP! WINS
Yi Moon-jung wins!
-Really?
-Whoa.
-Three wins in a row.
-She wins against the winner of CCW.
What I meant by an iron taste
wasn't just the intensity of it.
-It had to be under control. Like aespa.
-Control.
-She's right.
-In that aspect,
Chef Moon-jung's dish
was probably a little closer to it.
This means she will find a new teacher.
YOUR STUDENT DID NOT CHOOSE YOU
Who will it be? Sam stands up.
TEACHER! NICE TO MEET YOU
WINTER'S FINAL CHOICE: SAM KIM
He's now aespa's teacher.
-Sung-jun, you might be jinxed.
-This is crazy.
-Traumatized by idol stars.
-Yes.
He lost every single idol star round.
-Why are you so bad at idol star rounds?
-He's jinxed.
-It's because he gets too conscious.
-What now?
I feel so tacky today.
Chef Moon-jung, you're impressive.
-She has won three times in a row.
-That's amazing.
-Any thoughts?
-We couldn't stop her.
As always, I did my best
as if this was my last.
Thank you so much.
She's different when she cooks
and when she gives her speech.
-No Mala Acting Up!
-Someone else possessed her,
-and she's now back to herself.
-You don't seem the same.
-How uncanny.
-Right?
-Please put a star on Chef Moon-jung!
-Three consecutive wins.
-Congratulations.
-Undefeated!
-She came three times and won three.
-Witch With a Wok!
-Thank you.
Please take the tableware set too!
Congratulations, Moon-jung.
This is your third win in a row!
A round just for KARINA.
For the first time in the show's history,
they'll play as a team
with their right-hand men.
It's exhilarating
when teamwork is perfect.
It's in 30-second intervals.
-Thirty seconds?
-Grind the black pepper.
-Yes, Chef.
-Did you add lemon juice?
-I did.
Here comes his technique!
-That's so pretty!
-He's making a flower.
AMAZED
-Don't be nervous. We got this.
-Yes.
The teamwork of 14 years.
Salt!
SALT CROSS
PERFECT GROUP MOVE
NOT ONE TEAM WILL BACK DOWN
HOW WILL THE TEAM ROUND END?
This will be another fierce round.
Eun-yeong has won
all six rounds against him.
Poong isn't good
against authentic Chinese chefs.
This will be a hit-or-miss!
You can't give KARINA a stomachache.
I'm sure today will be different.
-What is that?
-Please!
IN SHOCK
TERROR
A VISUAL RIGHT OUT OF A WEBTOON
WHAT IS THIS BIZARRE DISH
THAT MADE KARINA SHUDDER?
She took a big bite.
She's like,
"Do I look like KARINA to you?"
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn